Guide to the William Shockley Papers SC0222
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-198
  - Audiovisual material
    - Audiorecordings
      - (Th) Side A: con JW Kirk-Patrick, Roy Secrest on Ekrlich Tape 33, Panetz USIA, JW Kirk-Patrick, [Tane?] Produce/ Side B: cont. [Tane?] Radio Ian [Carliss?], Carlin, Hatoyama DA, Panetz, Dudley, Davis Bryan Hills, Bill Ross SUDly, WCBS in NY, Iris Brest of SEC, 1974 May 19-21; 101.10.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (C) Side A: SU Daily Interview with Bill Ross/ Side B: Bill Ross SU Daily, 1974 May 20; 101.10.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (Th) Side A: Candy Stre, JJ McCaughan, Travis Osborne, Ch. 5 TV on Jap., Miele, WCB, Auerboch Tank (R)/ Side B: [Firing?] Line [Steibel?], Caroline Kittle, 1974 may 21-28; 101.10.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (L, T, C) Side A: Dudley Davis re Byran/ Side B: Intro, Start W=S, [Vie Cohn?], 1974 May 23; 101.11.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (L) Side A: W=S ends, Goldsby, Jamaican/ Side B: W=S on H-W, 1974 May 23; 101.11.2; 1 audiocassette(s); And discuss Byran Hills Debate (Box 101)
      - (L, C) Side A: [Bld Tht?] Close, Goldsby, LU Aud., in Lobby, Dr. Goodman, In car to NY/ Side B: Blank, 1974 May 23; 101.11.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (TV, C) Side A: In car from Byran Hills A.S., Dudley Davis & 2 former students/ Side B: CBS Wake-up, CBS, 1st [Illegible], 2nd, 3rd, [4th?], WCBS, "Com" re JRB, 1974 May 23-24; 101.11.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (T, R) Side A: JW Kirk-Patrick, Rolfe J. Averbach: Relevance for Tane Productions, Picasso, Inter, [Raceology Disrupt?], Freed & VSBP and (R)/ Side B: JWK re TI, Mead of WE Co, Van der Haag, Ron Secrest re SUDly, 1974 May 24; 101.11.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (T) Side A: John Saunders, JW Kirk-Patrick, Ron & Caroline, WCBS Ronnie Bennett [prder?]/ Side B: cont. Ronnie Bennett, HFW Office [Illegible], Thomas Abercrombie, Caroline Kittle, ABC Ellinton, Ron & Caroline, 1974 May 24-25; 101.11.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (C, C) Side A: Craig on arrival, Thomas & Delrita Abercrombie/ Side B: cont. Thomas & Delrita Abercrombie, Amoebas, 1974 May 25; 101.11.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - Side A: Pat Collins WCBS NY, 1974 May 25; 101.11.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (C) Side A: Abercrombie on Goldsby/ Side B: REad TS Eliot, Date Tom. (to elevators), [Cervase?], Delrita Abercrombie, Thomas Abercrombie, 1974 May 25-26; 101.11.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (C) Side A: cont. Thomas Abercrombie, McCaughan Conf., 1974 May 26-30; 101.11.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (Th) Side A: Caroline Kittle, Mr. Rader re conf. / Side B:cont. Rader, Tennesson Jack Corn Phone, ASSU Hausman, Patteson, Jack Corn, Frank Miele, Boh. Club Golf Res, 1974 May 28; 101.11.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (L) Side A: Virginia Poly, Inv. Trst - ExC-F Meth./ Side B: VPI, IT, ECE, 1974 May 6; 101.12.1; 1 audiocassette(s); Inv. Trstr - Ex. Cr.- Flk. Method (Box 101)
      - (PC, C) Side A: Sociology, Dept. VPI/ Side B: Press conf at VPI, 1974 May 6-7; 101.12.2; 1 audiocassette(s); End of Sociology Conf & Press Conf. VPI (Box 101)
      - (L, C) Side A: The VPI Lecture/ Side B: H. McGee, NCD, 1974 May 6-7; 101.12.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (C, R) Side A: Connie Blackwood, WLAC pre TV conf./ Side B: Marty O'Tools, [Demos thenian?], WLAC Trailer, Visit with Sidney Siegal of WLAC, 1974 May 7; 101.12.4; 1 audiocassette(s); Bad tape quality (Box 101)
      - (TV) Side A: WLAC, False Start, Real Start, TV Nashville/ Side B: Poet, 1974 May 7; 101.12.5; 1 audiocassette(s); WLAC Sidney Siegal & James Famer (Box 101)
      - (TV) Side A: cont. WLAC, WC Davidson & Mrs [Illegible], 1974 May 7; 101.12.6; 1 audiocassette(s); End of WLAC Dinner talk with Mr & Mrs W. C. Davidson (Box 101)
      - (C) Side A: cont. Stan Siegel conf., 1974 May 7-8; 101.12.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (TV, T) Side A: From TV set WCSC Stan Siegel, Nancy Hudson, Tennessean Permission, Stan Siegel, Satterfield Teleg, Nashville [Banner?], McCaughan/ Side B: Pary Sherman WMC-TV, [PA Teris Mary C, McCaughan Party, [Turgid Birch?], Cook sick, 1974 May 8; 101.12.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (C) Side A: McCaughan Party, [Most Hpprss?]/ Side B: McCaughan Party, 1974 May 8; 101.12.9; 1 audiocassette(s); McCaughan Party (Box 101)
      - (R, T) Side A: Athens O'Tools & UG Police, WLAC, Denosthenians in Chapel/ Side B: RTO, WRNG Neal Boorst & WS, WSB(NBC), Secrest re Ekrlich, MBS, APR WRNG, 1974 May 9-11; 101.12.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 101)
      - (L) Side A: U of Ga, 1974 May 9; 101.12.11; 1 audiocassette(s); U of Ga (Box 101)
      - (R) Side B: KTTU, 1974 Aug 30; 102.1.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: LA, 1974 Aug 30-31; 102.1.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: PDT, 1974 Aug 31; 102.1.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C) Side B: JLJ, 1974 Aug 31; 102.1.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: Dr. Hutchins/ Side B: at motel, 1974 Aug 31 - Sep 1; 102.1.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - Side A: HMC re Study, Swiss Ambassy, TRO Mobile W= S [unite?] Proposal/ Side B: Livingston Car, Townsend, Ralph, 1974 Sep 1-2; 102.1.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: ELS re MBS/ Side B: cont. JWK & JJ McCaughan, W=S Summary, 1974 Spe 2-4; 102.1.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T, TV) Side A: Keith Davy, ELS, [Carchill?], Lillian Hodison, Kohko KGBS/ Side B: Ch. 13 the Killers, Micheal E. Levin, 1974 Sep 4-5; 102.1.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: Hal Parets, Larry Attebery STTV, Talbert of Case, FNH Robinson/ Side B: cont. F.N.H. Robinson, Bob Graham, Robinson, Bruce [Strapper?] re Trstr Book, Katie McCaughen, J.W. Kirkpatrick cont., 1974 Sep 5-6; 102.1.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: J. W. Kirkpatrick, Seff Talbert of Case - WR, WINS, Bergen CWRU, Talbert/ Side B: cont. Tablert CWRU, GSL, ELS, Talbert (How come), Orem, Bill Loeb, 1974 Sep 6-10; 102.1.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: Cont. Bill Loeb, Cleve Press, Jas Ellison, Cleve Plain Dealer/ Side B: Jane Ellison, Bud Weidenthall, Tape & Rpy [Illegible], Talbert, Weidenthrall, Ellison Cleve Pl. [Illegible], Lou Rubenfeld, 1974 Spe 10-11; 102.1.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: JWK & JJ McCaughen, Hal Parets/ Side B: cont. Hal Parets, Mrs. Page, Make Culbert, Ellis Page, 1974 Aug 16-18; 102.2.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Ellis Page, CCC, Gary Hahn re Parets, Perry close son, GSL/ Side B: cont GSL, Hal Parets, Perry, Hal Parets, Mrs. JW Leslie in Office, Leslie, Prof. J. W., 1974 Aug 18-21; 102.2.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont J.W. Leslie, Off. L. D. Head CI & Long, JT, Olshen [Illegible], Sam Fok/ Side B: Cont. Sam Fok, KTTV, CCC McGuniss, [Fraas?], JT Chao SRI, CCC Durward S Reggs, 1974 Aug 21-22; 102.2.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Hal Parets re KTTV, Possony, Orem to Fraas/ Side B: cont. Orem to Fraas, Pinkerton for R. Graham, Stickneys, Pinkerton, Hal Parets, 1974 Aug 22-25; 102.2.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (D) Side A: RI Intro, W=S, [Illegible] seq, RI/ Side B: Dr. Williams, Block [Payds?], 1974 Aug 23; 102.2.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (TV) Side A: KTTV in LA - Meet Dr. David Sachs/ Side B: End TV, 1974 Aug 23; 102.2.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Hal Parets, DSquel, Commonwealth Radio, Off 1 wk & Riggs, JWK & JJ McCaughan, Graham/ Side B: Jim Davis, Berkeley Gaz, Graham, Sec, hall Jinkdrich, Rob Graham, 1974 Aug 25-27; 102.2.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T, C) Side A: cont. Rob K. Graham, JJ McCaughan, JWK off, RKG, KGBS, LA, Davey Rosen, Fraas/ Side B: cont. Fraas, Hal Parets, Vint by Fraas, 1974 Aug 27; 102.2.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Fraas, Keith Davey re [Illegible]/ Side B: JWK & JJ McCaughan, KTTC Atteburg, [Miersman?], Alan Greene, 1974 Aug 27-29; 102.2.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: Alan Greene, TRW, KGBS Kolko, JL Jones, JL Jones, BTL Fotenot, Keith D. & ELS, Sam Fok/ Side B: cont. R. C. Shockley, Phil Jones, Mod. Medicine, Repub. Phones, ?, Larry Rosen re Karen Morgenstern, SJSU Admin Justice, 1974 Aug 29 - Sep 23; 102.2.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (R) Side A: KGBS Kolko, JLJ Jr., KGBS Mickie-Teddi, Statement, Re D. [Illegible], 1974 Aug 30; 102.2.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (TV) Side A: Monte Rio, 1974 Jul 21; 102.3.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: Bohemia, Palo Alto Diag., 1974 Jul 21-30; 102.3.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Kartzman APBoo, Van de Walle, Parets, Jue McNiven, Alan Burk Show, WPIX, Townsend/ Side B: cont. Townsend, Oren, 1974 Jul 29-31; 102.3.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - Side A: Orem, Cachillac, Ross Aken, [Art Brown ?] Cad., Mrs. Worthen, El Cerrito Police, Barry/ Side B: [MAUG?] Mrs. Orem, Orem $, Jim Davis, TV Recorder Dutton, Zazarinde, FLorence Dix, 1974 Jul 31; 102.3.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Barry Cameron, El Carrito Police, Bant Dix, LEvy, Barry C., Art Brown Cadillac/ Side B: cont. Art Brown Cad., Alan Walker, Leukemia, Wang, McCaughan, 1974 Jul 31 - Aug 5; 102.3.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Orem, McCaughan, Galy McCall [Illegible] Line Transcript, Ron/ Side B: cont. Hal Parets re, Carol Dorey, Mary C, Ron Secrest TSC, Scott Thacher, CLS to end, 1974 Aug 5-7; 102.3.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Bill Loeb, Tennant Bryan, [Jeuk?] Jones, [Discairs?] TSC, Rent Keith, Bill Loeb/ Side B: Lem Pomeroy Editor, Teller RM Nixon via GSL, Philip Citron re Rice, Ron Secrest, Freeman [Illegible], 1974 Aug 7-9; 102.3.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Dr. Hosford, Ron Secrest, Miele, Wrong No., McCaughan, MBS, McCaughan/ Side B: cont. McCaughan, FLorence Dex, Keith re day off, Hal Parets re [Illegible], Keith re RMO, Ron Secrest good bye cont., 1974 Aug 9-12; 102.3.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Ron Secrest, Bernie Ringland, Roger Freeman Off., Office re. Dex, [Mansinger?] Sec., Hal Parets/ Side B: Parets, Mrs. Dix, Arthur P. Fraas, Oak Ridge, 1974 Aug 12; 102.3.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Fraas AP, Joe McCaughan, Mrs. Dix after Read WFB, Orem [Illegible], Mrs. Orem, 1974 Aug 12-13; 102.3.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: ? Crothers Hall, Am Pro by Caudill re, UCLA, AUG Offic, Provost Doris, Rockly re FREED/ Side B: Keith re overtime, ELS & Keith, McGinnis CCC, Dorn's Auto, Keith on WFB [Illegible], MIke McGinnis comes Club 2 calls, 1974 Aug 13-16; 102.3.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: GR Lynch, Alverz mtg., Berk [Gag?], GRL, Reese Wells V. Ga, Al Wang/ Side B: cont. Al Wang, GSL, MBS, Keith, Kim Berglind, AP Bu, Ron Keith, Al Wang on JTR at 77 degree K, 1974 Jun 17-20; 102.4.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Al Wang, [Jane?] Anerbach, Tane, Ron & Keith, Dr. Robt. Meyer re MBS/ Side B: cont. Dr. R. Meyers, MBS, Victoria Chertak, Family ", MBS, Dr. Meyers to end, 1974 Jun 20-22; 102.4.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Mrs. McCaughan, Reg. Orem/ Side B: Orem, JW Kirkpatrick, Office, Gary Kriger, Coast Mag, 1974 Jun 22-24; 102.4.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: W. Alvarez, Ralph Townsend, GSL re FREED, Tane Auerbach, GSL / Side B: GSL re IRS, Coast Mag, Photo Krager, Coast Andrews, Kruger Geo Stevens, 1974 Jun 24-26; 102.4.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Geo Stevens, Gloria Weins Lecture BU, John [Litner?], Al Wang, Now OK, Frank Miele/ Side B: cont. Miele, MBS can leave, Philips Nobile, WH Long, 1974 Jun 26-27; 102.4.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. WH Long, Joe McCaughan/ Side B: cont. McCaughan, Cho, Charean Forsberg, MBS, 1st day home from Hoop, 1974 Jun 28-29; 102.4.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: MBS, ELS & MBS, MBS, Mary Gold Koehler/ Side B: Koehler, Al Wang, Frank - Taider, Com. Club J. Page, Albert Devon, 1974 Jun 29 - Jul 2; 102.4.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: [Camino?] Coin Gold, Flynn taping, Sandy from An & Jason Lumish after [Illegible] dinner/ Side B: cont. Sandy - Jason, Nobile Synde, Ron & Keith, Ralph Townsend, 1974 Jul 5-8; 102.4.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Ralph Townsend, Ada [Bgrnes?] BTL, Am. Pro BU, 1974 Jul 8-10; 102.4.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Motorola, Off. Keith and Ron/ Side B: cont. Ron Secrest, Nobile, Bryan, Cosmos, HFW off., Joe McCaughan, 1974 Jul 10-11; 102.4.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Joe McCaughen, [Caudill?] off., HFW re $, Keith Davey, 1st contact with Harry M. Caudill/ Side B: cont. Caudill, PA Diag., Art Brown, [Doris?] Elliot, Citron, Am. Pro. BU, Marsha Kartzman, 1974 Jul 11-29; 102.4.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - Side A: Sye Jones, ELS, 1974 Oct. 15; 102.5.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (L) Side A: SU Chinese Assos. Sam Fok, W=S "The Moral Obl. Diag. Am. N. Trag. Stat. IQ Def", 1974 Oct 16; 102.5.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (L) Side A: Dr. Nancy Wade SJSU, 1974 Oct 16; 102.5.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (R) Side A: WWR/ Side B: WWR, 1974 Oct 17; 102.5.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th, R) Side A: cont. WWR, Jeff Talbert/ Side B: cont. Jeff Talbert, Col. Danny White, FCM, Ellis Page re Skeptic (ELS), 1974 Nov 17-18; 102.5.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: cont ELS Page, Prof. Ellis Page on Skeptic Article by W=S, 1974 Oc 17; 102.5.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Hal Parets, Caroline Kittle/ Side B: Cadillac, MBS, Cadillacs, Cortes, GSL off., Syl. Jones, 1974 Oct 19-21; 102.5.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Frost, Cavalier (Cath. Std. Pap U Va)/ Side B: Frost, Ug Va, T Bryan off & Cadilac Rote, Rector Cad., Bryan Off, GSL, Syl. Jones, 1974 Oct 21-22; 102.5.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Syl. Jones (at Ricky's), Gary Hahn, Dan Groen, [Schlossam?] Son/ Side B: Mel [Scholossman?], Tennant Bryan, Howard Frost U of Va, 1974 Oct 22-24; 102.5.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (L) Side A: Calif. Inventors Council, W=J Lecture "Creative Failure", 1974 Oct 23; 102.5.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Howard Frost U of Va, Cavarlier/ Side B: Howard Frost, Syl. Jones, Dave Nakamura, Schlossman, 1974 Oct 24; 102.5.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: Am. Soc. Cent. [Illegible] re, Syl Jones (Mod. Med.), & Christopher Springman (photo), 1974 Oct 24; 102.5.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Bill Loeb, Skeptic Burnette, Mrs. Spicer, Frost Stn Papter U Va/ Side B: cont. Frost U of Va, Ted Kruger, WWR Dalles Nancy Goodman, Phil Jones, Mod. Med., Ted Kruger, 1974 Oct 6-7; 102.6.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Ted Kruger, Nancy Goodman, HFW $, Ken Jackson BTL, John Trever/ Side B: cont. John Trever, [Schlumberger?] FCH, Dave Makamura, HFW, Cadillac, [Shlumberger?], Jensen, Skeptic, 1974 Oct 7-12; 102.6.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Tnj) Side A: Tobia, Dr. Peter, Young PA, JB Cortes "Turn on Tape", "Psychopathy" / Side B: Great Talent, New [Illegible], Paul Ramsey, John Trevor, Res. Crime, 102.6.3; 1 audiocassette(s); Tobias Am. Pres. Org. (Box 102)
      - (R, Th) Side A: Jerrsen, USC Mollrich, Syl Jones/ Side B: cont. Syl Jones, FCh [Schlumberger?], Jim Crow sec, MIT [Barnett?], WRR, 1974 Oct 12-17; 102.6.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Tnj) Side A: Joe McCaughan, When, Beni [Nonlleg?]/ Beni, Orem, Pat Reynolds, 1974 Oct 12; 102.6.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Tnj) Side A: Frank Miele, Cortes (GSL) "Guts Racist", JB Creads "Concern", Frank Miele, YPO/ Side B: cont. YPO Annette, Mrs. Peter Tobia, 1974 Oct 12-13; 102.6.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Tnj) Side A: ARJ, Geo Jones, Peter Tobia (Young Presidents Assoc.)/ Side B: cont. Peter Tobia, Peter & Annette YPO, AR Jensen, 1974 Oct 13; 102.6.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: Peter Tobia, Ruth Beni, MET. Club Conf, Start Cortes/ Side B: Met. Club Conf., 1974 Oct 13-14; 102.6.8; 1 audiocassette(s); End of Tobia YPA Met. Club DC Conference (Box 102)
      - (C) no title, 102.6.9; 1 audiocassette(s); Met. CLub DC Conference (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: MET Club, 1974 Oct 14; 102.6.10; 1 audiocassette(s); Met. Club DC Conference (Box 102)
      - (C, T) Side A: cont. Met. Club/ Side B: Herty [Neok?], [Gerards?] Beni, TJ [Rogey?] & ELS, 1974 Oct 14; 102.6.11; 1 audiocassette(s); End Met. Club DC Conference (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: cont. Conf. call Whelan-Beni, Calvin (Kline) of Oakkenoll, Hal Parets/ Side B: Parets, Talbert, G. Beni, Forum Contemp. History [Barlett?] Publisher, 1974 Sep 17-20; 102.7.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C, T) Side A: Bartlett F. Cont. Hist., Justice Dept Stuart Smiths, Gay Boston, [ Conf Suburban?]/ Side B: cont. Whelan, Russell, Calvin of Oakknoll, Room Seri, Jerry [Glasoman?], Seton Hall Lawyer, Labor Relations, 1974 Sep 20-22; 102.7.2; 1 audiocassette(s); Gerry Glasoman UAL II Forum Cont. Hist (Box 102)
      - (C) Side A: Jerry Glasoman UAL II/ Side B: Toll Call, DA, 1974 Sep 22; 102.7.3; 1 audiocassette(s); Jerry Glasoman on UAL II (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: RT Osborne, Prof. Moore of SJU, Admin. Justice SJU, Maida U.Md, Wolfgang, Med. McKay, Cortez/ Side B: cont. Jaun Cortez, Wolfgang sec., ?, Prof. Marvin Wolfgang, 1974 Sep 23-24; 102.7.4; 1 audiocassette(s); (U of PA) Marvin Wolfgang Jaun Cortez (Georgetown) Follows Aug 29 (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Wolfgang, Ligens Office/ Side B: cont. Ligens, McKay-Salgado PA Times, Shah Better Kutzke, [Pres?] AI Barnett, 1974 Sep 24-26; 102.7.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Arnold I. Barnett MIT, Corning of Hoover Inst., JJ McCaughan sec./ Side B: Gay Boston, FB, Joe Carlson, Ted H. Kruger, 1974 Sep 26-28; 102.7.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Ted H. Kruger, [Illegible] St. Denis, LH Roth office, Dep. Jus., LL Heston/ Side B: cont. LL Heston, Dan Groen, MIT Mrs. Khan, GS Leonard, 1974 Sep 28 - Oct 1; 102.7.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. GSL, Syl Jones [Illegible], Al Wang, FCM, Danny Stern UCLA/ Side B: cont. Danny Stern, APB, Ted Kruger, Schlumberger FCH, [Schacter?] Off., Cortes, 1974 Oct 1-3; 102.7.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Jaun Cortes, Jesuit, Integ. Bomb, RBC, Lesser, Agree Guts, [Three MB?], Bibb Latane, 1974 Oct 3-4; 102.7.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Mel [Schlosoman?], Tennant Bryan, JLJ off., T. Waring off., Henry [Olsben?], Lou Schnitzler [Catt.?], Barnett MIT/ Side B: Slossman, Barnett MIT, 1974 Oct 4; 102.7.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Barnett, Tennant Bryan, Skeptic Schumberger/ Side B: cont. Skeptic Schumberger, Dahlke of Wash., Ted Kruger, Bill Loeb, 1974 Oct 4-6; 102.7.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (I) Side A: [Illegible], Hoddenson History Interview, 1974 Sep 10; 102.8.1; 1 audiocassette(s); Am. Phys. Soc. History Lillian Hoddenson at BTL (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: Lou Rubenfeld APB, Observer - Bergen - Stein - Talbert - Williams, TV Ch. 13 Day & Guiger Rogers/ Side B: Day at Night, Guiger Rogers 30 Challenges, [Subarban Air?], Bad Weidenthal, 102.8.2 (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: cont. Bad Weidenthal, Jane Ellison, Cleve Plain Dealer, ABC re [Woeuled?] Knee, Miles Culbet/ Side B: Talbert, Stern re [Illegible], Ulcer, [Illegible] McVales, 1974 Sep 12; 102.8.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T) Side A: Jeff Talbert/ Side B: cont. Jeff Talbert, CWRU, 1974 Sep 12-15; 102.8.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (DEB, PC) Side A: Press Conf. cont., Case Western Reserve Union Debate/ Side B: cont. Debate, 1974 Sep 15; 102.8.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (L) Side A: [Illegible], Observer/ Side B: Disruption, 1974 Sep 15; 102.8.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (R, D) Side A: Dean Schuele, 1974 Sep 15-16; 102.8.7; 1 audiocassette(s); WERE Debate Innis (Box 102)
      - (R) Side A: WERE Innis- Shockley, 1974 Sep 16; 102.8.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (R) Side A: WERE Radio Cleveland Innis-Shockley, 1974 Sep 16; 102.8.9; 1 audiocassette(s); Innis-Shockley Debate WERE (Box 102)
      - (TV, T) Side A: Misc. Ch. 13, Ch. 8 [Milky Famegas?], Ch 3 AL Fesher, [Illegible] Schaulrock, [Reciditiom?], W=S Reads & Bill S/ Side B: 1st Tape, 1974 Sep 16; 102.8.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (T, TV-C) Side A: in NBC Studio Royal Kennedy, Al Fisher, John M. Whelan/ Side B: cont. John M. Whelan, Dr. & Mrs. [Bomi?], Conference call Beni & Whalen, 1974 Sep 16-17; 102.8.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (L) Side A: Civil Engr. Forum W=S, Cedric X/ Side B: Raises Hair - Test Tube, Olin Jones, 1974 Dec 17; 102.9.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: ARJ, Ch 9, Jeff [Littleboy?], Dale Thomas/ Side B: Wilhelm, Dale Thomas, Ron Moskovitz, 1974 Dec 18-19; 102.9.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Ron Moskwitz, Syl Jones, Miele, Cecil Baber/ Side B: cont. Cecil Baber, McGrady Tape, H. Parets, IBM Prob. HFW, H. Parets, 1974 Dec 19-20; 102.9.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: H. Parets, Cecil Baker's Off, Gary Hagn, Cervase Sennett, SU Rev., Cecil Baber/ Side B: Cecil Baker, W=S - FT, Dave Nakamura, 1974 Dec 20-23; 102.9.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Geo. Rawson, ELS re M. Mod, [Pard Lynder?], Ruth Beni/ Side B: cont. Ruth Beni, Syl Jones re His Mod. Med. MS/ Side B, 1974 Dec 23-24; 102.9.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Syl Jones, Paul Solmon "Real Paper"/ Side B: cont. "Real Paper", Mike Culbert, MBS, Syl Jones, 1974 Dec 24-26; 102.9.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Syl Jones, MM, ARJ, PAY Boat loose/ Side B: Gary Hahn, GH, Fid. Found., Gary Hahn, 1974 Dec 26-30; 102.9.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Gary Hahn, Laurel Thor goodbye, Al Wang, Pac. Tel. $/ Side B: Terman, MBS, ELS, Stanford Rev. Sennett, Syl Jones, Mod Med, 1974 Dec 30 - 1975 Jan 2; 102.9.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: cont. Syl Jones Mod Med, ABC News on Watergate, Sennett, NBC, Creative Village, Stanford Rev. Clark, Manning, Herrell/ Side B: WP Herrell, Mr. Hahn Un. Repub., Dick Shockley, 1975 Jan 2-5; 102.9.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Dick Shockley, M Cre $1000 RKG, Bev yates off., [Cattermole?] re FS/ Side B: Yellow Cab, Jim Angell, Mrs. Washam, 1975 Jan 5-7; 102.9.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Mrs. Hahn re [Illegible] JW Walters, HF Weyher, Ron Tuttle SU Bonds, Syl Jones/ Side B: cont. Syl Jones, 1975 Jan 7-8; 102.9.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (TV, T, C) Side B: Ruth Beni, Mrs. PJ Kernt, Ruth Beni, ABC Demo Convent, 1974 Dec 1-6; 102.10.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
        Graphs and Notes were left in Box 102.10 in regards to a few of the tapes inside.
      - (Tnj) Side A: ABC TV, Ruth Beni re [Cervese], Cervose, John Trevor/ Side B: John Trevor, John Cervose, John Trevor, 1974 Dec 6-9; 102.10.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (C, L) Union Club cont., 1974 Dec 9; 102.10.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (L) Union Club NY Trevor, 1974 Dec 9; 102.10.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)
      - (Th) Side A: Cho, Parets [Illegible], Parets re FNL/ Side B: Graham off, Graham, Dick Shockley, 1974 Nov 29 - Dec 10; 102.10.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 102)